<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bubble Hub</string>
    <string name="On">On</string>
    <string name="Off">Off</string>
    <string name="ConnectToBubbleHub">Connect To Bubble Hub</string>
    <string name="available_devices">Available Devices</string>
    <string name="disconnect_from_bubble_hub">Disconnect From Bubble Hub</string>
    <string name="bubble_hub_connection">BUBBLE HUB CONNECTION</string>
    <string name="mix_mode">Mix Mode</string>
    <string name="fade_split">FADE SPLIT</string>
    <string name="fade">FADE</string>
    <string name="lights">LIGHTS</string>
    <string name="sleep">Sleep</string>
    <string name="cancel_sleep">Cancel Sleep</string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="startScanningCapitalLetters">START SCANNING</string>
    <string name="stopScanningCapitalLetters">STOP SCANNING</string>
    <string name="Bubble_Pillar">Bubble Pillar %1$d</string>
    <string name="Bubble_Wall">Bubble Wall %1$d</string>
    <string name="searching_for_bubble_devices">Searching For Bubble Devices</string>
    <string name="custom_color">Custom Color</string>
    <string name="custom">Custom</string>
    <string name="BUBBLES">BUBBLES</string>
    <string name="Small_Bubble">Small Bubble</string>
    <string name="Small">Small</string>
    <string name="Pillar_Bubble">Pillar Bubble</string>
    <string name="Pillar">Pillar</string>
    <string name="Pyramid_Bubble">Pyramid Bubble</string>
    <string name="Pyramid">Pyramid</string>
    <string name="LIGHTS">LIGHTS</string>
    <string name="FADE_SPLIT">FADE SPLIT</string>
    <string name="Rainbow_2">Rainbow 2</string>
    <string name="Rainbow_1">Rainbow 1</string>
    <string name="FADE">FADE</string>
    <string name="SOUND">SOUND</string>
    <string name="small_plus_big">Small + Big</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_play_stop">imageButton for play/stop</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_volume_down">imageButton for volume down</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_sound_on_off">imageButton for sound on/off</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_sound_next">imageButton for sound next</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_volume_up">imageButton for volume up</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_mute">imageButton for mute</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_sound_previous">imageButton for sound previous</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_bluetooth_mode">imageButton for bluetooth mode</string>
    <string name="image_button_sd_card_mode">imageButton sd card mode</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_usb_mode">imageButton for usb mode</string>
    <string name="image_button_for_aux_mode">imageButton for aux mode</string>
    <string name="Big_Bubble">Big Bubble</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_type_image">bluetooth type image</string>
    <string name="report_bugs_or_leave_feedback_and_suggestions">Report bugs/leave feedback and suggestions</string>
    <string name="not_now">Not now</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="number_of_attachments">Number of attachments: %1$d</string>
    <string name="attach_images">Attach Images</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="main_location_permission_warning">This application requires location permissions in order to function. Please grant location permission.</string>
    <string name="grant_location_permissions">Grant location permissions</string>
    <string name="brightness">BRIGHTNESS</string>
    <string name="brightnessPercentage"> %1$d %%</string>
    <string name="centerpiece">Centerpiece %1$d</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_page_not_found"><![CDATA[<h2><font color="red">Help Page Not Found.</font></h4> ]]></string>

    <string name="help_page_info">
     <![CDATA[
     <p>
     <b>Connection Issues: </b> Please follow these steps if you are having connection issues such as devices not showing up on the main screen.<br/> <br/>
     <b>1.</b> Make sure that the phone Bluetooth is turned on. <br/> <br/>
     <b>2.</b> Make sure that the device is turned on and is in Bluetooth range of the phone. <br/> <br/>
     <b>3.</b> Make sure that the device is not connected to another phone. <br/> <br/>
     <b>4.</b> Make sure the manual button on the device is not turned on. <br/> <br/>
     <b>5.</b> Make sure you granted location permissions on your phone when the application asked for it.  <br/> <br/>
     <b>6.</b> Try to restart your phone and the device that you are trying to connect. Some of the devices will have a switch on them.
     If your device does not have a switch, simply unplug its power cable and plug it back after 5 seconds.
      <b> Please see location permission paragraph below for more information.</b> <br/> <br/>
     </p>
     <p>
     <b> Location Permissions: </b> This application might ask the user to grant access to device`s location on some of the newer Android phones.
     This permission is necessary to access the Bluetooth capabilities on some of the phones. This application does not collect any user data and
      we do not share or collect any location-based information from the phone. The permission is simply necessary for the application to be able
      to connect to the Bubble devices.
     </p>
     ]]>
 </string>

    <string name="bubble_pillar_help_page_info">
     <![CDATA[
     <h2>Bubble Pillar Buttons Explanation</h2>

     <h4><font color="blue">Control Buttons</font></h4>
     <p>
         <b> On/Off: </b> Turns the system on or off. <br/><br/>

         <b> Sleep: </b> Starts the sleep timer. Bubble pillar will shut down in 30 seconds unless you turn off the system
         or press the <b>Cancel Sleep</b> button. The timer that appears to the left of sleep button indicates when Centerpieces
         will turn off.
     </p>

     <h4><font color="blue">Lights Buttons</font></h4>
     <p>
         <b> Fade: </b> Bubble pillar lights switch to fade mode where both top and bottom lights will have the same color.
         The lights will continually fade from one color to another in a predetermined manner. <br/><br/>

         <b> Fade Split: </b> Bubble pillar lights switch to fade split mode where the top and bottom lights will have different colors.
         Top and bottom lights will continually fade from one color to another in a predetermined manner. <br/><br/>

         <b> Custom Color: </b> You can choose your desired color from a color wheel and Bubble pillar will set both top and bottom lights to your desired color.
          <b>NOTE: You must either let go of the color wheel or hold your finger at the same color for a short period of time
          in order to send the command to bubble pillar to change to your desired color.</b> <br/><br/>

         <b> Mix Mode: </b> Periodically switches between fade and fade split lights modes. <br/><br/>
     </p>

     <h4><font color="blue">Bubble Hub Connection Button</font></h4>
     <p>
         Some of the other Bubble products(bubble wall for example) will send radio signals to all other Bubble products in order to make
         controlling of multiple Bubble products easier.Press the <b>Disconnect From Bubble Hub</b> button if you want to prevent some particular
         Bubble Pillar from listening to radio transmissions from other Bubble products.
     </p>

     ]]>
 </string>

    <string name="bubble_wall_help_page_info">
     <![CDATA[
     <h2>Bubble Pillar Buttons Explanation</h2>

     <h4><font color="blue">Control Buttons</font></h4>
     <p>
         <b> On/Off: </b> Turns the system on or off. <br/><br/>

         <b> Sleep: </b> Starts the sleep timer. Bubble wall will shut down in 30 seconds unless you turn off the system
         or press the <b>Cancel Sleep</b> button. The timer that appears to the left of sleep button indicates when Centerpieces
         will turn off.
     </p>

       <h4><font color="blue">Bubble Buttons</font></h4>
     <p>
         <b> Small Bubbles: </b> Use only small bubbles <br/><br/>

         <b> Big Bubbles: </b> Use only big bubbles <br/><br/>

         <b> Small + Big: </b> Use small and big bubbles simultaneously. <br/><br/>

         <b> Pyramid Bubble: </b> Produce various shapes by using a combination of small and big bubbles. <br/><br/>

         <b> Pillar Bubble: </b> Switches bubble mode to produce various shapes by using a combination of small and big bubbles.
          <b>NOTE: You might hear the water overflowing into the water reservoir depending on the height of the water inside the panel.
           This is a normal behavior as long as the alarm is not turning on or you are not seeing any water leakage.</b><br/><br/>

         <b> Mix Mode: </b> Periodically switches through all bubble modes. <br/><br/>

     </p>

     <h4><font color="blue">Lights Buttons</font></h4>
     <p>
         <b> Rainbow 1: </b> Bubble Wall lights switch to rainbow 1 mode. <br/><br/>

         <b> Rainbow 2: </b> Bubble Wall lights switch to rainbow 2 mode. <br/><br/>

         <b> Fade: </b> Bubble Wall lights switch to fade mode. The lights will continually fade from one color to another in a predetermined manner. <br/><br/>

         <b> Fade Split: </b> Bubble Wall lights switch to fade split mode, where top and bottom lights will have different colors.
         The lights will continually fade from one color to another in a predetermined manner.. <br/><br/>

         <b> Custom Color: </b> You can choose your desired color from the color wheel and Bubble Wall will set the lights to your desired color.
          <b>NOTE: You must either let go of the color wheel or hold your finger at the same color for a short period of time
         in order to send the command to Bubble Wall to change to your desired color.</b> <br/><br/>

         <b> Mix Mode: </b> Periodically switches through all the lights modes. <br/><br/>
     </p>

     <h4><font color="blue">Audio Control Buttons</font></h4>
     <p>
         Audio controls should mostly be self-explanatory with one exception. If you choose the USB mode, SD Card Mode or
         AUX mode without having USB, SD Card or Aux cable connected to the speaker, the speaker might switch to an FM radio mode.
         You can either provide the necessary connections for the mode you want to use or switch to Bluetooth mode where you can
         pair your phone with the speaker and stream your desired content to the speaker.
     </p>
     ]]>
 </string>

    <string name="bubble_centerpiece_help_page_info">
     <![CDATA[
     <h2>Bubble Pillar Buttons Explanation</h2>

     <h4><font color="blue">Control Buttons</font></h4>
     <p>
         <b> On/Off: </b> Turns the system on or off. <br/><br/>

         <b> Sleep: </b> Starts the sleep timer. Centerpieces will shut down in 30 seconds unless you turn off the system
         or press the <b>Cancel Sleep</b> button. The timer that appears to the left of sleep button indicates when Centerpieces
         will turn off.
     </p>

     <h4><font color="blue">Lights Buttons</font></h4>
     <p>
         <b> Fade: </b> Centerpieces lights switch to fade mode. The lights will continually fade from one color to another in a predetermined manner.<br/><br/>

         <b> Custom Color: </b> You can choose your desired color from a color wheel and the centerpieces will set the lights
         to your desired color. <b>NOTE: You must either let go of the color wheel or hold your finger at the same color for a short period of time
          in order to send the command to the centerpieces and change the lights to your desired color.</b>
     </p>

     <h4><font color="blue">Brightness Slider</font></h4>
     <p>
        With brightness slider, you can control the brightness of the centerpieces. Setting the brightness slider to 0 will keep the
        Centerpieces bubbles running but will turn off the lights. <b>NOTE: You must either let go of the brightness slider or hold your finger
        at the same brightness level for a short period of time in order to send the command to centerpieces to change to
        your desired brightness.</b>
     </p>

     ]]>
 </string>


</resources>
